[{"answer": "Do you have any other old records besides these", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Who does", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "As always", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I wonder if he's just totally insane and he really thinks a bus is coming or", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What was that all about", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I didn't get it either", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "C'mon my friend, I'm trying to collect data here! Don't you want me to find you your perfect dream girl", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Every guy has a type", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "He does that every single day", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Can I get you a..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "YES", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Not the my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Wow, this is so cool..", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I dunno... because I can't stand the idea of a world where a guy like you can't get a date..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Are you kidding? It's a dream job! I can't believe you got a job like that without even trying... God, I wish that was my job..", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "When are you finally going to get your diploma", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm sick of waiting", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Don't you want nice stuff", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Uh... hello", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh, hi..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Are you trying to get me wasted so you can take advantage of my womanly charms", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "\"Yeah, righ", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "How long have you been up", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Do you want to go get breakfast somewhere", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We really should get together sometime soon... ", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No... no, it's just that I should get going in a few minutes, and", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What's her problem anyway?  Did she actually tell you you couldn't see me", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What does she mean by that", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " So, do you like me, my friend", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "In whatever way you think I mean", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't think you understand how I really feel about you, my friend", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Nothing. Don't worry, I won't bother you any more", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You know what we should do? Let's go get in your car right now and just take off! We could just drive away and find some new place and start a whole new life... fuck everybody", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'll drive, then", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't think I'm in any condition to drive", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "So where would we go", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'll drive, then", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Who cares? Let's just go... what's stopping us", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I dunno, I..", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "What do you want", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I'm serious! I'm just so sick of everybody! Why can't I just do whatever I want", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What do you want", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Please let me come with you. Please please please..", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Of course it's a good idea... it's our plan", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "She's not at home", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What the fuck is she doing?! She was supposed to be here three hours ago", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Uh, do you mind if I wait? I really need to talk to her", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Why would she be hiding from me", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "my friend!? Why would she be with my friend", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Why? What did she tell you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "On that pathetic fake blind date", "docId": "Ghost-World.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Didn't she ever tell you about that? God, she really is pathological..", "qsentId": 52}]